

NICOLAS JUNCAL

SOFTWARE ENGINEER

ABOUT

I am a full stack software engineer with a background in business and finance advisory.

I'm a team player and love sharing my experiences and working close with my colleagues and clients. I believe working well with others shows that you are committed to achieving both personal and organisational goals.

PROFESSIONAL SKILLS

Typescript

JavaScript

Python

NestJS

Express/Node.js

ReactTS/JS

CSS/HTML

SQL/MySQL

GraphQL

Playwright

Github Jenkins

AWS/New Relic

Dynamodb

CONTACT

Sydney, NSW







in /nicolasjuncal

WORK EXPERIENCE

SOFTWARE ENGINEER

IAG Limited (client) Nov 2021 - Current

We developed a versatile quote and buy app for major brands like ASB, NRMA, ANZ, and BNZ, using a microservices architecture to cater to over 75 brands. My role was crafting brand-neutral code for seamless brand integration. Built on a tech stack of ReactTS, DynamoDB, and Typescript, and incorporating Playwright for end-to-end testing and CI/CD, the app combines reliability and efficiency. Hosted on AWS with NewRelic for performance optimization, we delivered a scalable, high-performance solution to meet each brand's unique digital needs.

WORKSHOP COORDINATOR Berendsen Fluid Power | May 2019 - Aug 2021

Managed a team of eight to refine workshop processes, enhancing efficiency and precision. Collaborated with IT experts to integrate Fujitsu's RunMyProcess ERP, seamlessly merging it with our operations. This key initiative advanced our process automation and data management, showcasing our commitment to technical excellence and reliability."

BUSINESS MANAGER

Bold Int | Sep 2018 - Jan 2019

Engaged in the sales of IT services, including outsourcing, software factory, and IoT. Part of a cross-functional team, I play a key role in strategically shaping solutions that cater precisely to IT stakeholders' needs. My focus is on blending technical expertise with a customercentric approach, ensuring that each solution is both innovative and aligned with specific client requirements.

EDUCATION

SOFTWARE ENGINEERING IMMERSIVE

GENERAL ASSEMBLY | 2021 - 2021

MASTER OF BUSINESS ADMINISTRATION

KAPLAN | 2018 - 2019

BACHELOR OF BUSINESS ADMINISTRATION WITH IT

FIAP | 2010 - 2015